mightynest.com 2019-04-25

# Privacy Policy - MightyNest

## MightyNest Privacy Policy Last Updated May 23, 2018

MightyNest is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy addresses how MightyNest Inc. collects and uses information you provide. By visiting MightyNest.com, and providing your information to us, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

MightyNest.com is built with features designed to protect information that we obtain from you and utilizes relevant encryption software and other safeguards to ensure our e-commerce site is safe. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information.

**What Information is Collected**  
The information we collect during use of MightyNest.com is grouped into two categories: personal information, which is information that is identifiable to a specific customer, and aggregate information, which is general information that does not identify an individual customer. Personal information may include your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information and phone number.  MightyNest does not store any credit card information directly on our servers. Other personal information you may share with us if you choose to complete a subscriber profile includes items such as birthday, green living preferences (e.g. vegan, preferred fragrances, etc), and details about your home (e.g. have pets). We may also collect certain demographic information such as your Site preferences, household information, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education (some of this information may be optional). MightyNest may use or disclose aggregate information for any purpose.

**How We Use Your Information**  
We collect personal information to make our services related to this Site (the “Services”) more rewarding for you to use, including recommending products, selecting surprise subscription items, billing, shipping and tracking your orders. If we have any questions or concerns regarding your order, we may use this information to contact you. We also use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers’ preferences and improving customer experience on the Site. We may also use your information to contact you for promotional purposes and provide customer service to you. If you enter into a sweepstakes, contest or similar promotion, we may use the information you provide to administer those activities. We may combine information about you with information from other sources in order to improve the quality of our Services.

We also receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information, which is collected passively using various technologies, and cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Services. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve you, we often conduct research on customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the personal and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. We may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

You may receive periodic emails from us with information on new products, specials, or upcoming events. If wish to be removed from our mailing list, please let us know by emailing customerservice@mightynest.com with your full name and email address.

If you are a member of one of our subscription services, you may also receive periodic emails from us with information about the products you received in your subscription box, reminders of upcoming orders processing dates, and the seasonal specials reserved for members. If you wish to be removed from these notifications, please let us know by emailing customerservice@mightynest.com with your full name and email address.

### **How is This Information Shared**

MightyNest does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. We may share your information with your consent. MightyNest may share data with trusted partners and service providers to help provide backup and disaster-recovery services, provide data storage and processing services, perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to MightyNest, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

There are certain circumstances in which we may share your personal information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  1. **Customer Experience Improvements:** We may share information about you with trusted third parties in order to improve your customer experience.
  2. **Third Party Advertising Partners:** We may share information about you, such as your name, address, email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us via our third-party advertising partners and its service providers, in order to deliver to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. Our advertising partners will make the data we provide to it anonymous. To learn more about the use of this information or to make choices about receiving personalized advertising provided by third parties, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking here.
  3. **Change of Control:** Please also note that we do reserve the right to transfer your Personal Information and other information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control. In such a circumstance the Transferee would be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.
  4. **Sweepstakes:** If you submit your email address to be added to a mailing list or Sweepstakes or other promotion, we will use the email address for the sole purpose of sending you announcements, special offers from MightyNest along with Site, App, and Store updates. Each email we send will contain information on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list. You can also unsubscribe by sending an email to customerservice@mightynest.com.
  5. **Referrals:** If you elect to use our referral services for informing a friend about our Site, App, or Store we ask you for the friend's name and email address. MightyNest will automatically send the friend an initial email inviting them to visit or transact with the Site. MightyNest may also send additional emails reminding your friend that you referred them. Additionally, you may send a reminder email to your friend to remind them to sign up. MightyNest stores this information for the sole purpose of sending these referral emails and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact MightyNest to request the removal of this information from our database and to stop receiving a Reminder.
  6. **Other Reasons:**
    1. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of MightyNest, its users or the public.
    2. As required by law, to comply with a judicial proceeding or court order, to exercise our rights, or to defend against any claims.

### **Cookies and Web Beacons**

This Site uses cookies and web beacons to gather aggregated, non-personally identifiable information in order to help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of this Site users have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. Such information may be shared with trusted third parties but the information will not personally identify you. To the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information. As we develop this Site, we may gather additional information from you through the use of other technologies. The Site may use cookies in on-line catalogs to keep track of your status and contents of your shopping cart. or to retain information gathered in cookies to allow you access to password-protected areas of the Site. You may set your browser to decline cookies. If you do so, however, you may not be able to fully experience some interactive features of the Site.

### **Use of Your Personal Information**

MightyNest collects and uses your personal information as described in this Statement or disclosed to you in our services, to operate its website(s), and deliver the services you have requested. For example, we may use your information to:

  * operate and improve our internal operations, systems, products, and services;
  * understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience and enjoyment using our services;
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * link or combine information about you with other personal information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better and more personalized service; and
  * protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.

MightyNest may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from MightyNest. MightyNest may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

### **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to collect anonymous information about how you use this Site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our Site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave our Site. The cookies are not connected to your personal information. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of this Site’s features.

### **Web Beacons**

Web beacons, or clear gifs, are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. Web beacons help us better manage content on our Site by informing us what content is effective. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to your personal information. We use web beacons to track activity on our website and emails  to understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

### **Analytics**

Third parties who provide us with analytics services for the services may also automatically collect some of the information described above, including, for example, IP address, access times, browser type and language, device type, device identifiers and Wi-Fi information. Please consult the respective privacy policies and statements of these third parties for more information, including how Google Analytics, Visual Website Optimizer, Disqus, Olark, and KISS Metrics use this data.

Google Analytics Advertising uses a featured called Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. 

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information or sensitive data through MightyNest’s public comments or reviews, this information may be collected and used by others. We encourage you to be careful with how you use these services. You may opt out of analytics tracking by using your browser's "do not track" feature. If you would not like to be tracked by analytics software, we encourage you to consider the Google Analytics Opt-Out tool here https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/. 

### **Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you provide sensitive information (such as a credit card number), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). For further privacy, we encrypt all requests to MightyNest.com using SSL. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of such information. 

MightyNest will not be liable for disclosures of your Personal Information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. Due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, MightyNest cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or any information provided online, and you do so at your own risk. Users must accept all risks associated with any data transmission, including the risk that their Personal Information may be intercepted in transit.  
If you have any questions about security on our Site, please contact us as indicated below.

MightyNest takes reasonable steps to help secure your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, use, alteration, destruction, or disclosure. Personal information we collect may be stored and processed in your region, in the United States or in any other country where we or our affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers maintain facilities. We maintain primary data centers in the United States. We take steps designed to ensure that the data we collect under this Statement is processed according to the provisions of this Statement and applicable law wherever the data is located.

### **International Visitors**

The Service is hosted in the United States and is intended solely for visitors located within the United States, Canada and Australia. If you choose to use the Service from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information outside of those regions to the United States for storage and processing, and by providing your personally identifiable information on the Service you consent to that transfer, storage, and processing. Please note that the United States does not have the same data protection laws as the European Union and other regions.

### **Opting Out**

We may occasionally send you newsletters and emails regarding special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates. We may also communicate with you on behalf of third parties about special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates we think may be of interest to you, or you may have opted-in to receive newsletters or special promotions from us. If you decide you do not wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link or by following the unsubscribe instructions included in the communication. Note however that as user of the Services you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Services, such as billing or service notifications. You may also opt-out of certain targeted advertising by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices.

### **Links to Other Sites**

This Site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information that you disclose to such sites or that they may collect. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there. This Site may enable you to post comments, reviews and other information on publicly available areas of this Site. Any information you post in these areas of this Site will be available to all of our users, so please use caution in disclosing any personal information when you post such comments, reviews or other information.

### **Facebook, Instagram, and other Social Media  **

If you participate in any of the activities on our blog, you can log in You can log in to your account using your Facebook account, or utilize your Facebook account to access and use the social features on this Site. In doing so, Facebook will ask your permission to share certain information from your Facebook account with this Site. This may include your first name, last name, and email address. This information is collected by Facebook and is provided to us under the terms of Facebook’s Privacy Policy. You can control the information that we receive from Facebook using the privacy settings in your Facebook account. If you use your Facebook account to access and use the social features on this Site, your Facebook user name and your Facebook profile picture will be shared with other users of this Site. Further, other users of this Site may be able to view your profile, engagement with blog posts, and shopping activity on this Site. Some actions you take on our blog may be visible to users on this Site who have a Facebook account but who might not be your friend on Facebook. The information you choose to share with your Facebook friends will be attributed to your Facebook account that was used to access this Site. Facebook’s use of such information and any information it collects from your use of Facebook is governed by Facebook’s Privacy Policy. MightyNest has no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Facebook that may be enabled within use of this Site. The use of information on this Site is governed by this Site’s Privacy Policy. You understand and acknowledge that you have read and are familiar with this Site’s Privacy Policy and Facebook’s Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to share your activity on this Site with your friends on Facebook, you may adjust your sharing settings on this Site at any time to disable such sharing. You understand and acknowledge that if you adjust your settings to disable such sharing on Facebook, such activity may continue to be publicly available to other users on this Site, including users with Facebook accounts.

### **Updating or Deleting Your Online Account Information**

You may update or correct your online account information at any time by logging into your account and navigating to the “My Account” page or by contacting us. You can also contact us by phone if you wish to deactivate your account, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

### **Children Under 13**

Children under 13 may view this Site, but they cannot make a purchase or provide any personal information. This Site is not designed for children and we do not wish to collect personal information from children under 13. If you register with us and we discover that you are under 13, we will delete your account. You must be 18 or over to purchase any products from this Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors. If a child under age 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we as a parent or guardian to contact us and we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

### **Exclusion to This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to MightyNest through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as review sections and forums (collectively, “Public Areas”), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and MightyNest shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

### **Amendments or Modifications to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Notice of any change will be posted on this Site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

### **Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding the use of our Site or Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
MightyNest Inc  
Attn: Legal Department/Privacy  
8044 St Louis Ave  
Skokie, IL 60076  
Or 1-847-905-0567
